picasion.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy Policy - Picasion - Create GIF animations online - Make an Animated GIF

| 

**_Picasion: Animated GIF maker_**  
Create Animated GIF online for free! Upload your pictures or grab them from Flickr or Picasa Web, make avatars or funny animations and post them to MySpace, Hi5, Facebook, eBay, Orkut, Bebo, Digg, QQ, Friendster, etc. No need for Flash. 

Create animated avatar or MySpace avatar at Picasion (animated gif generator/tool/maker/animator)! 

| 

This Privacy Policy sets out the data processing practices carried out through the web by the PICASION website. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact us. 

### Information collected

Protecting your personal privacy is very important to us, PICASION.com collects no personal information about you other than that which you choose to provide when you use the website, have questions or need help with a particular issue. No individual identifying or personal information (such as your name) is automatically gathered when you visit Any Page of PICASION.com 

### Use of personal information

No personal information is collected by the PICASION.com website at the moment. 

### Disclosures

PICASION.com will not disclose or use any of your information unless required to do so by a law enforcement agency. 

### Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. PICASION.com website might use cookies.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

### Other web sites

Our web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you that will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

We may revise our privacy policy from time to time without notice.

_Last updated: Dec 3, 2012._

---|---
